[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 20]
Qiu.
We're all safe now.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
I want you to feel
the pain of losing your loved ones.
I'm fine.
I'll be okay in a minute.
Just give me a minute.
Qiu,
I thought this time
I could finally protect you.
No.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
Don't.
I failed again.
Qiu,
do you still remember
how to break immortality?
If I die,
does that mean we truly love each other?
No.
I don't want this!
You can't die!
I...
No!
I don't love you!
Qiu...
I want a hug.
Let me hug you.
Qiu...
Qiu.
You're...
free now.
No!
I don't love you.
Ning Changyue, I don't love you.
I don't love you, Ning Changyue!
I don't love you!
No!
Ning Changyue!
♪ Why do you insist on finding me? ♪
Coming.
Why did you drink so much?
Does your head hurt?
Here.
Let me massage it.
♪ You know I didn't want to stay ♪
How is it?
Better?
That's what you get for drinking so much.
♪ You hold me tight ♪
Regret it now?
♪ But I am fading away ♪
Let's go.
I don't want to go.
Why are you so lazy?
You little lazybones.
I don't want to go.
Alright, alright.
♪ You hold me tight ♪
Once we're done,
I'll take you out for some nice food.
Sound good?
♪ I lose my way ♪
You're back.
I'm out of battery.
I can't move.
Need to recharge.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
No, not fully charged yet.
Charge a little longer.
That's enough.
Need more.
♪ Will you still think of me? ♪
I need more. Not full yet.
Why is there a fish missing?
I want a cuddle.
Give me a cuddle.
♪ Do you know I was afraid? ♪
Forget the fish.
Beg me, and I'll cook for you today.
♪ When you used to hold me tight ♪
Please, babe.
Call me hubby.
♪ I lost my way right then ♪
Please, hubby.
Give me a kiss.
Oh, stop it.
Fine...
We're having beef today.
We made a promise.
We have to watch it together.
Watch it bloom.
Ning Changyue,
you liar.
Aunt Song,
have you...
not eaten for days?
How about...
we go out for a walk?
[Three Months Later]
Over here.
A little more here.
Okay.
Nice and red.
So pretty this way.
Right?
Perfect.
Just stay here with us
and enjoy the sunshine.
Qiu.
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
I bet you didn't expect this.
I saw everything.
You finally go out today.
And you're in a bad mood.
Let's just forget about everything for a while.
And...
have a drink to relax.
Okay?
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Do you remember the last time
you were here?
Seriously,
you were the craziest person I've ever seen.
You were so cute.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Song.
This is Eternal Vows Wedding Planning.
Mr. Ning Changyue
booked a full wedding package
with us
three months ago.
The venue and catering are all set.
The wedding is scheduled for next week.
We just wanted to confirm
if there are any changes on your end.
Ms. Song?
No changes.
Alright.
I won't bother you any further.
Have a great day.
Idiot.
You started preparing three months ago.
Qiu,
marry me.
♪ Writing all over your walls ♪
Ning Changyue,
at first,
I thought immortality was a reward.
♪ I was here but now I must leave ♪
Like the gods favored us,
stretching out our time inch by inch,
so we could have each other forever.
But later I realized
time never deepens love on its own.
Sometimes it wears down the passion,
and dilutes the thrill.
It makes the earth-shattering romance
slowly fade into the mundane routine of daily life.
During that time,
♪ I won't fall in a cage ♪
I thought I had lost it.
♪ Missing old days ♪
I thought I forgot
♪ I will be here, I will stay ♪
what love
truly is.
♪ Let them judge as they please ♪
♪ There will be brighter days ♪
♪ I will stay ♪
Ms. Song Yiqiu,
before the vows,
on behalf of Mr. Ning Changyue,
I'd like to give you a gift.
Hi!
It's Wu Ya here.
Welcome to my uncle's
secret wedding prep vlog!
Let's go!
My uncle
has been acting super sneaky lately.
I have no idea what he's up to.
Let's go check it out together.
Uncle!
Are you planning to propose?
Are you?
♪ Two mismatching souls ♪
Tell me!
Give me the phone.
♪ We never saw it coming ♪
No! I'm going
to tell Aunt Song now!
Hand over the phone!
♪ Forever is shorter than we thought ♪
If she finds out,
-I'll kill you! -No!
No way!
Stay still.
♪ The fading shadows of our love ♪
What's this?
♪ Echoing endlessly in the dark ♪
Qiu's ring size.
Come with me to buy the ring.
You used this to measure Qiu's finger?
♪ Don't cling to what should have been ♪
She's going to be your aunt.
Isn't this a bit sketchy?
Sketchy?
♪ We can't keep fighting for a ghost ♪
Mind your own business.
Where can I find a tape measure?
♪ This empty house isn't a home ♪
Hurry up.
I can't hold this shape much longer.
Let's go.
♪ I think it's time to let us go ♪
This is Aunt Song's ring finger, right?
♪ Admit it ♪
♪ What we already know ♪
Give me a sec.
First time getting married,
♪ We can't keep fighting for the ghosts ♪
he lacks experience.
Song Yiqiu,
will you...
Stop.
Your eyes are too stiff.
♪ We can't keep fighting for the ghosts ♪
You look like an AI.
Come on, what do you want from me?
♪ This empty house isn't a home ♪
Uncle,
you need to be sincere.
Keep it natural.
♪ I think it's time to let us go ♪
Make her feel your heartbeat.
♪ Admit it ♪
♪ What we already know ♪
♪ We can't keep fighting for the ghosts ♪
Qiu,
we
spent 3000 years together,
from being immortal
to becoming ordinary people now.
I want to ask
can I be the one
who stays by your side,
and makes you happy every day?
I love you.
Uncle,
I actually
didn't record
any of that.
My phone died.
I just wanted to see
how long you'd practice.
I'll love you forever!
I'm going to...
Can't catch me!
Forgot to turn it off!
But right now...
I think I understand again.
It's just the subconscious habit
of wanting to call your name every time I turn around.
It's the napkin you always have ready
whenever I pop open a beer.
It's the way, over thousands of years,
you never hesitated
to run toward me.
Immortality may end,
but love
is eternal.
Ms. Song Yiqiu,
do you
take Mr. Ning Changyue to be your husband?
For better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
to love and to cherish?
Qiu.
♪ Willing to give up immortality ♪
♪ To share these joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Who cares how absurd eternity may be ♪
♪ I'd trade this life for eternity ♪
♪ Then we'd be complete ♪